[{"answer": "Actually I was just thinking of your analogy, I was thinking Ron Paul is sort of a Shemp.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "And why he compares the GOP field to the Three Stooges?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "As is evidenced by this interview no.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "Are you -- are you a funny person by nature?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't say extraordinary.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Was that one of the most extraordinary experiences in your life?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "You -- it was really not just a long day but it was a day full of family, full of friends, full of people from the industry, from the government, Governor Christie, Mayor Booker.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "It was a long day, it was full of -- a lot of celebration as well as grief, but how would you describe it?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "You know, to any singer, that would be devastating.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "How big a blow do you think it was to her that she lost the power of her voice and couldn't hit the great notes she used to hit?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, I think with all these cases, it's a matter of she paid the price for what she thought she used to want.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "For you, what did you think?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Well, it's not illegal to be a party girl.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Do you know anything about that?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, physically, she changed.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "How did she change from the woman you saw?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Partly but addiction is not as Dr. Drew, who treated me, by the way, successfully, it's not about -- it's not a character defect, it's not a moral problem, it's, you know, something wrong with your brain, to put it simply.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Whitney just never seemed to have the desire to rehabilitate herself, to actually get proper treatment for this, did she?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "'BRIEN: No.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "When you saw -- I don't know if you did see, but in the run-up to the day she died, for a few days, pictures emerging from Hollywood nightclubs of her falling out and looking disheveled and so on, did you fear that something awful would happen?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Not really because I don't -- I don't know what she was doing and still we don't have the toxicology reports yet.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Doesn't that ring alarm bells?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "I think they've said no.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "We don't now either way, right?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Where was everybody when she was on this chaotic, spiral downhill.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Barely two weeks ago?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we were all surprised on 9/11.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "What is happening while America sleeps?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Usually not.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Yes, but it's nowhere near, it's nowhere near in terms of financial firepower, anything like Mitt Romney's, and it kind of reminds me of that campaign Meg Whitman fought in California, because money in the end can't overcome personal deficiency, can it, as a candidate?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "It really disappointed me and I was very clear about it.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "I mean that is hypocritical, isn't it?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, if you really look at the book carefully, I'm far more favorable about the president than critical.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Where do you think he's really been going wrong or where would you give him due credit?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "No, I'm really not.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "You're not feeling the surge?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Steve.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Steve, isn't it?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "About 140 times.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "You appeared how many times on Johnnie Carson?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Yes, Bob Hope was the most, and I was the second most.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "That has to be a record, isn't it?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Well, Charlie Hartsock and Vance DeGeneres, who are my partners at Carousel, had this idea to kind of trace the -- trace comedy in terms of generations and -- and how it cross-pollinates and sort of look to people's inspirations.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "What was the idea?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "-- of superstar comedians, isn't it?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I don't know if it's a definitive history of comedy, but it is --", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "How are you -- how are you billing it?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "It's unique in the way in which the comedians talk about what they do.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "On what makes people laugh?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "That never happened.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "That happened between you and him?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "It's so subjective.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Is there a stat -- when you all get together?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "s it evidenced by this interview, no.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Are you -- are you a funny person by nature?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "But biggest comedian would your great burning ambition as a kid, was it?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Let's talk a little bit break, gents.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "And if it's funny, then, you know?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "But you do -- do you thank God every day that these things happen?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "There -- there is no Moe and Larry here.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "It's a little bit like that, isn't it?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "It will hide your own lack of character, right?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I would take Alan Arkin.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Who -- if I could trap you both on a desert island separately and you could have one comedian with you to make you laugh for the rest of your days, who would you take?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Because he makes -- one-to-one, he makes me laugh more than anyone I've ever met.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "He is -- he's so dry and so acerbic, he just -- I love being around the man.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I'd probably take Groucho.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Who would you take?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "It's much, much better to be rich and famous.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "If you're honest, did you prefer life before, when you were more anonymous, or have you actually embraced the whole fame thing with great enthusiasm?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "It's a lot tougher to deal with, I think, if you get that kind of thing when you're younger.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "I like to think it might have been, but you never know, you know?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Do you miss the character?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Oh, not in a million years.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "ARELL: And I'm writing a symphony and I have a cooking show coming up.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "You've got seven movies on the go, is that right, over the next two years?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Did you ever imagine here you'd be in Hollywood in your smart power suit, in the middle of a seven movie extravaganza --", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "A billion dollars.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "-- earning you, potentially, a billion dollars?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "I'm always pinching myself.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "You must pinch yourself a bit, don't you?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "You need to have had cigarettes burned on you for years, don't you, to be genuinely -- to make an audience laugh?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "You said that Billy's timed to go with his Oscars appearance, right?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "It was before that.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 727, "question": "Eddie Murphy was probably doing it then, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 726}, {"answer": "It's so -- I -- you know what, I think David is the best interviewer because he puts people at ease.", "docId": "120220pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "I get the sense you've got great chemistry between you?", "qSentId": 735}]